

## ANUSHKA WIJEGOONAWARDANA

### **ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

■ : +94 711 971 313
■ : anushkaduwolka123@gmail.com

♥: 132/6 1st Lane Nahena Hunupitiya, Wattala.

## **About Me**

Dynamic & adaptive software developer with 2+ years of experience in the software development industry, By working in a startup organization I gather lots of industry-related experience from communicating with the clients, setting up the domain & server environments to develop & deploying the web applications. I am most familiar with Javascript related technologies & looking forward to upscaling my knowledge & provide my best service for your organization.

## **Experience**

#### **III** WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER

#### **Meridian Creative Solutions**

March 2019 to November 2020

- Interactive, customized and responsive front end application development using various cutting-edge technologies.
- Communicate with client & teams to gather information & help them to deploy applications in a live environment.
- Creating support documents for the end-users & clients to explain the application process & backend data handling.
- ■ Developing and managing the customize WordPress plugins for the more advanced client requirement.
- Helping fellow subordinate to troubleshoot, debugging errors & deploying applications.

#### **III** INTERN WEB DEVELOPER

#### Sure We Make

February 2018 to March 2019

A startup branding agency located in Rajagiriya. I started as an intern web developer.

- Customizing the WordPress & HTML templates as per the giving UI design by the & setting up the plugins & services that needed to the end product.
- ■ Setting up the Domains & Servers, Deploying websites into the servers, managing the website security such as SSL & Email hosting.

GitHub: / AnushkaWijegoonawardana97 Website: / www.wijegoonawardana.com



## ANUSHKA WIJEGOONAWARDANA

### **ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

■ : +94 711 971 313 : anushkaduwolka123@gmail.com

♥: 132/6 1st Lane Nahena Hunupitiya, Wattala.

### **Education**

#### **BCS HIGHER EDUCATION QUALIFICATION (BCS)**

**BCS The Chartered Institute For IT** 

2018 - 2020

- Subjects: Software Development, Information System, Network Technology, Database System, Object Oriented Programming, Principles Of Internet Technologies, Professional Issues in IT.

## SOFTWARE DESIGNING & FINALIZING CERTIFICATE (NETBEANS) IIAC Campus Colombo 2017

- Software designing using visual paradigm or MySQL workbench

#### CCE ADVANCED LEVEL EXAMINATION

St. Joseph's College Colombo 10

2016

## **FAMILIER TECHNOLOGIES & TOOLS**

#### A NATIVELY FLUENT PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGIES

# HTML

**CSS** 

Bootstrap

■ JavaScript

**J**Query

**★** AJAX ★ React JS

■ Wordpress

**Strapi** 

**I** NPM

**⊯** PHP

**■** Sass

JSON

# ♣ CONVERSATIONALLY FLUENT PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGIES

**⊯** Java

Mr C

■ Node JS

**Firebase** 

**★** Webpack

GitHub: / AnushkaWijegoonawardana97 Website: / www.wijegoonawardana.com



## **ANUSHKA WIJEGOONAWARDANA**

### **ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

🛚 : +94 711 971 313 🔻 : anushkaduwolka123@gmail.com

**Q**: 132/6 1st Lane Nahena Hunupitiya, Wattala.

♣ TOOLS & EXTRA

**★** Photoshop

Adobe XD

■ Netlify

# Heroku

**Projects** 

\* SPECTRA BROADBAND WEBSITE \* TRU RIDE WEBSITE

REF: www.spectradev.us

**★** GENESIS MOTORS WEBSITE

REF: www.genesismotors.com.au

\* STUDYINSL WEB APPLICATION

REF: www.studyinsl.com

**★** CEYLON EMPORIUM WEBSITE

REF: www.ceylonemporium.com.au

REF: www.ridetru.com

HONEST GREENS ASIA WEBSITE

REF: www.honestgreens.asia

**★** SKOOLEEO WEB APPLICATION

REF: www.skooleeo.com

**★** CTH WEBSITE

REF: www.capitaltrust.lk

Check out my portfolio website www.wijegoonawardana.com for more details.

### REFERENCE

🚨 DESHMANYA DR. VIRAJ PINTO JAYAWARDENA

Managing Director at MATRIX Institute of Information Technology (Pvt) Ltd

No: 4, Bambalapitiya Drive, Galle Road, Colombo 04. +94 71 431 79 27 viraj@matrixtes.com

Mr VIRAJ ADHIHETTY.

Chief Executive Officer Meridian Creative Solutions (Pvt), Ltd

No: 3 Dharmaraja Road, Alfred House Avenue, Colombo 03. +94 759100544 viraj@wearemeridian.com

GitHub: / AnushkaWijegoonawardana97 Website: / www.wijegoonawardana.com